‫Hello, and welcome to the
‫AWS Certified Developer Associate Course.
‫My name is Stephane Maarek, and I will be your instructor.
‫So we're starting in five minutes.
‫Let's just go over some prerequisites.
‫So we're going to prepare for the DVA-C02 certification,
‫and although it's a challenging certification,
‫I will try to make this course as interesting as possible
‫to cover everything you need to know.
‫And as such, we will cover over 30 AWS services.
‫So we have a lot to learn, but don't worry,
‫we'll go step by step.
‫Even if you're an IT or an AWS beginner, you're welcome,
‫but take your time, this is not a race,
‫and haggle with me with the hands-on.
‫You don't need to be a developer to pass the developer exam,
‫but it definitely helps to have some coding background.
‫Now, if this is your second AWS certification
‫and you've done the
‫Certified Solutions Architect beforehand,
‫try not to skip any lectures.
‫After the seventh section, yes, there are some new content
‫regarding the Certified Developer exam,
‫but please review the first lectures.
‫It will be always good for you
‫to rehash that basic knowledge.
‫Okay, so what about me?
‫So I've passed the certification twice,
‫so once in 2018, and I scored with 984, so only one mistake,
‫and then, very recently, in April 16th, 2020,
‫I've scored again 982.
‫I wanted to make sure that this course was up to date,
‫and trust me, it is.
‫I've updated all the lectures that needed to be updated
‫to pass the exam with flying colors in 2020.
‫So what's AWS?
‫If you're new to this, this is a cloud provider,
‫and with the AWS, you're able to have services and servers
‫that can be used on demand and scales very easily.
‫This has allowed companies
‫to run a website for, say, millions of people,
‫with only three or five engineers, which is crazy.
‫So AWS has revolutionized IT over time,
‫and now it powers some of the biggest websites in the world
‫that you know of, for example,
‫obviously Amazon.com, but also Netflix.
‫So this course is very complete.
‫We'll be learning all of these things and more,
‫and this may be daunting at first, but don't worry,
‫we'll go step by step.
‫Don't feel afraid.
‫But as you can tell,
‫there's a lot of things we have to learn in this course.
‫So I like to call AWS a spaghetti bowl
‫because it is a complete mess,
‫but we'll try together to navigate through it
‫and together learn all the services we need
‫for you to become an AWS certified developer.
‫So thank you so much for watching,
‫and I will see you in the next lecture.