‫So just a quick lecture about course review. Very shortly
‫Udemy will ask you to give your opinion about this course and ask that you put a star rating. The star rating
‫represents the entire course overall not just if you like what you've just seen
‫So basically these reviews, they mean a lot to me.
‫And they represent your opinion about the course. They're super important and I would love one from you
‫but if you're not ready to rate the course.
‫Just click on "ask me later" and the prompt will come back maybe half an hour or an hour later.
‫Overall in this course we're going to start by the fundamentals.
‫And so if you're already a certified solutions architect you can skip the few fundamental lectures or sections
‫or you can just watch them if you want a quick refresher.
‫OK.
‫I really hope you'll enjoy this course.
‫I will see you in the next lecture.